l told him I'm addicted to pedicures...
(Raj:)...and he told me
he lost his virginity to his cousin.
(Howard:)She was my second cousin.
(Sheldon:)And the first woman you ever disappointed
sexually. Bada-buzzinga!
(Raj:)Oh, yeah. And then there was the time when
Leonard and I took Howard to Las Vegas...
(Raj:)...and paid a hooker
to pretend she was Jewish...
(Raj:)...and that she wanted
his little kosher pickle.
Of all the "Howard humping hooker"
stories, that one's my favorite.
(Howard:)Okay, buddy, that's it. Sit down.
Oh! Oh.
(Raj:)Oh, what about that tubby girl in
the Sailor Moon costume at Comic-Con?
(Howard:)Don't remember. Please sit down.
(Raj:)The only threesome
l've ever had in my life...
(Raj:)...and I'm proud to say
it was with this man right here!